<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Archie</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Archie</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Athul</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Syntax Higlighters</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/langs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/langs/</guid><description>Python def sum(a,b): return a+b print(f&amp;#39;The Sum of 4 and 5 is {sum(4,5)}&amp;#39;) JavaScript const sum = (a,b)=&amp;gt;{ return a+b } console.log(sum(4,5)) Go package main import ( &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; ) func addition(a int, b int) int { return a + b } func main() { x := addition(4, 5) fmt.Println(x) }</description></item><item><title>Hugo shortcodes</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-6/</guid><description>Images Dave Herring Dave Herring Github Gist Youtube video Tweet Hugo 0.24 Released: Big archetype update + @Netlify _redirects etc. file supporthttps://t.co/X94FmYDEZJ #gohugo #golang @spf13 @bepsays
&amp;mdash; GoHugo.io (@GoHugoIO) June 21, 2017 Vimeo Callouts 💡 I guess this works</description></item><item><title>Telegram Bot for GitHub Actions</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/tg-gh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/tg-gh/</guid><description>Telegram Telegram is a cloud-based mobile and desktop messaging app with a focus on security and speed. It is free to use and extensively hackable. It also has a good bot support system. The API is also easy to implement and has many wrappers for building bots with the API.
GitHub Actions GitHub Actions is a CI/CD runtime for your GitHub repository. You can run almost anything from scripts to docker containers.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Traveling Ultralight</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-4/</guid><description>I’m on a trip at the moment, and a friend who generously let me sleep on his couch looked at my small travel backpack and commented on how little I travel with: “That’s impressive,” he said.
I was a little surprised, because though I’ve gotten that comment before, it’s become normal for me to travel with just a small bag (10 lbs. or less, usually), and I have friends who travel with even less.</description></item><item><title>Typography</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-5/</guid><description>Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.
Heading 1 Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio.</description></item><item><title>How I Learned to Stop Procrastinating, &amp; Love Letting Go</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-3/</guid><description>The end of procrastination is the art of letting go.
I’ve been a lifelong procrastinator, at least until recent years. I would put things off until deadline, because I knew I could come through. I came through on tests after cramming last minute, I turned articles in at the deadline after waiting until the last hour, I got things done.
Until I didn’t. It turns out procrastinating caused me to miss deadlines, over and over.</description></item><item><title>Fearlessness: How to Stop Running from Space</title><link>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://athul.github.io/archie/posts/post-2/</guid><description>We spend our days filling in every available space, cramming in more tasks, responding to messages, checking social media and online sites, watching videos.
We are afraid of empty space in our lives.
The result is often a continual busyness, constant distraction and avoidance, lack of focus, lack of satisfaction with our lives.
We run from silence. We run from the spaces between tasks and appointments. We run from solitude and stillness.</description></item></channel></rss>